lr.org 2017-11-29

# Privacy policy | Lloyd's Register

Lloyd’s Register understands and respects individuals’ right to privacy and is committed to providing on-line data security.

This privacy statement explains how data is handled whilst you browse and submit information through the website and your options regarding the ways in which your data is used.

## Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for records keeping purposes. Cookies are very common, being used to improve how a website works. Cookies contain information that can be used on particular sites and to tailor a visitor’s experience on the website or provide data that can be used for analysis by our web servers.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to disable cookies or to inform you when they are set. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our website if you disable them.

This website may use cookies to monitor website usage. This is statistical information allows us to manage and develop our website(s), for example to improve usability, or measure the popularity of a given web page. The information gathered does not identify you personally. Cookies cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites or damage your system.

Cookies we used and how we use them:

**Cookie name** | 

**Used for?**

| **Where?** | **Added to site**  
---|---|---|---  
  
_utma   
_utmb   
_utmc   
_utmz<>

| 

Used by Google analytics. Google analytics cookies do not collect personal data about you. [[Click here for an overview of privacy at Google](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)]

| Throughout site | 01/01/2012  
ASP.NET_Sessionid | 

This cookie contains the users session ID and the cookie will expire at the end of the session (when you close your browser). This cookie does not store personal data about you. [[Visit the Microsoft website](http://support.microsoft.com/kb/899918)]

| Throughout site | n/a  
visitor_id (duration 10 years) | 

These cookies collect information sales and marketing purposes to help improve visitor’s experience. [Find out more at pardot.com](http://www.pardot.com/company/legal/privacy-policy/ "Pardot Privacy policy"). The visitor cookie includes the name “visitor_id” plus the unique identifier for the visitor, ex: “visitor_id1234”. This cookie is set by our tracking code on website visitors. No personally identifiable information is stored in the cookie.

| Throughout site | 03/05/2014  
pi_opt_in (duration 10 years) | 

These cookies collect information sales and marketing purposes to help improve visitor’s experience. [Find out more at pardot.com](http://www.pardot.com/company/legal/privacy-policy/ "Pardot Privacy policy"). The persistent cookie named “pi_opt_in” is what we use to stay in compliance with the 'Do Not Track' initiative. No personally identifiable information is stored in the cookie.

| Throughout site | 03/05/2014  
visitor_id (duration 10 years) | 

These cookies collect information sales and marketing purposes to help improve visitor’s experience. [Find out more at pardot.com](http://www.pardot.com/company/legal/privacy-policy/ "Pardot Privacy policy"). Only set if the user is logged into the Pardot app as a user. No personally identifiable information is stored in the cookie.

| Throughout site | 03/05/2014  
  
For more information on cookies and how to set your browser setting to disable cookies, visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

Registration and completing forms   

If so required you may be asked to provide personal information such as your name, address, telephone number and credit card details when you complete an order form to purchase products or services or make an enquiry.

The information may be passed to the subsidiaries of Lloyd’s Register Group Limited responsible for the service/product requested by you.

Any information gathered will only be used to complete your request unless specifically stated on a particular form.

Information provided by you will be handled in accordance with the relevant jurisdiction’s data protection legislation. We maintain strict security standards and procedures with a view to preventing unauthorised access to your data by anyone, including our employees.

## Data for direct marketing

At each point of data collection individuals are given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving direct marketing activity. Where individuals do not want to opt-out of such communication, we may provide information on:

  * Services and products that may be of interest.
  * Changes and improvements to the website.

Should you decide to change your mind on not receiving such communications, contact our Data Protection Officer – details below.

## Transfer of data / sharing

We will not disclose your personal information unless we are obliged to do so or allowed to do so by law or where we need to do so in order to run our organisation (for example information may be passed to and used by other subsidiaries of Lloyd’s Register Group Limited or where other people process data for us (some of which may be outside the UK and/or EU)). Should this be the case, we will ensure that confidentiality agreements in line with applicable data protection legislation are in place.

## Amend/update information

If you believe that any information held by us about you is incorrect or incomplete you should write to the Data Protection Officer at the address given below. Any information which is found to be incorrect will be corrected as soon as possible.

## Other web sites

Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this privacy statement.

The operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Notification of changes to the Privacy Statement

We may change the content of service found on our site at anytime without notice and consequently our privacy policy may change at any time in the future.

## Access rights

You have the right to access personal data that is held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you please write to the address given below.

The Data Protection Officer (UK & Global),   
C. Colby-Blake   
Lloyd’s Register Group Services Ltd   
71 Fenchurch Street, London EC3M 4BS, UK   
E: [chad.colby-blake@lr.org](mailto:chad.colby-blake@lr.org)   
T: +44 (0)20 7423 1724

For Singapore:   
The Data Protection Officer   
Joyce Wun   
Lloyd’s Register Asia   
1 Fusionopolis place #9-11 Galaxis   
Singapore 138522   
E [joyce.wun@lr.org](mailto:joyce.wun@lr.org)   
T +65 3163 0581
